Finding Aid for the Herbert Charles Sanborn Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Correspondence - Incoming, Incoming correspondence of 4,326 letters, 235 post cards, and 70 telegrams. Alphabetically arranged, letters are typescript, holograph, and carbon copies. There are several circular and mimeographed. 1 Letters signed with initials only and with 1 name only are found at e
  - Hart, Henry G. (1), May 18, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Hart, Joseph Kinmont (2), Dec. 2, 1934, Dec. 10, 1934 (Box 6)
  - Hart, Laura Louise (2), Dec. 13, 1934, Apr. 27, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Haskell, HenryS. (1), Apr. 15, 1932 (Box 6)
  - Haun, Mildred (1), Dec. 30, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Haurin, Ena (1), May 28, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Havel, Richard C. (1), Jan. 15, 1951 (Box 6)
  - Hayes, Douglas (7), Dec. 22, 1949, Dec. 27, 1949, Jan. 16, 1950, Mar. 7, 1950, Apr. 24, 1950, Jan. 31, 1951, Aug. 9, 1951 (Box 6)
  - Hayes, Wayland J. (1), Sept. 23, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Haying, Fred W.S. (1), Sept. 19, 1948 (Box 6)
  - Hearn, Mr. and Mrs.John R. (1), Apr. 15, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Heath, Lorraine (1), July 20, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Heidelman, Julia L. (1), Jan. 2, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Hein, R.F. (1), May 28, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Heinlein, Christian Paul (12), Feb. 23, 1941, June 16, 1943, Apr. 12, 1944, Apr. 20, 1944, Sept. 8, 1944, Oct. 9, 1944, Oct. 23, 1944, Nov. 1, 1944, Nov. 24, 1944, Dec. 1, 1944, July 22, 1946, Nov. 21, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Heinsohn, A.G.Jr. (2), Aug. 9, 1966 (to E.L. Bartlett), Sept. 13, 1966 (to Albert Gore) (Box 6)
  - Held, William W. (4), Dec. 20, 1933 (telegram), May 18, 1934, Feb. 4, 1935, Sept. 19, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Helms, C.L. (1), (n.d.) (Box 6)
  - Helsel, Paul R. (1), Dec. 14, 1949 (Box 6)
  - Henderson, Edgar H. (1), May 4, 1927 (Box 6)
  - Henderson, Florence (1), Nov. 26, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Henegar, Bernard (1), Dec. 2, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Henneman, Richard H. (1), Feb. 16, 1950 (to John B. Wolfe) (Box 6)
  - Henry, N. (1), Nov. 24, 1959 (Box 6)
  - Herd, Sans Faute (1), May 24, 1944 (post card) (Box 6)
  - Herod, W.E. (2), Mar. 1, 1950, Mar. 28, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Herzfeldt, Lotte (1), Feb. 18, 1948 (Box 6)
  - Hewell, Mrs. G.T. (1), Sept. 18, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Hichborn, Franklin (2), June 3, 1955 (to J. Lester Miller), June 6, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Higgins Nancy Mead (1), Apr. 30, 1932 (Box 6)
  - Hilbert, Thekla (1), Feb. 22, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Hill, Grace B. (6), May 15, 1952, July 22, 1955, Dec. 3, 1955, Jan. 25, 1956, Jan. 15, 1959, Mar. 4, 1959 (Box 6)
  - Hill, Henry H. (1), Oct. 12, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Hill, J.H. (1), Feb. 8, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Hill, Mildred L. (5), Aug. 16, 1950, Nov. 15, 1950, Dec. 30, 1950, Jan. 6, 1951, Sept. 28, 1951 (Box 6)
  - Hille, Sue (1), Apr. 21, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Hilliard, R.L. (1), Aug. 23, 1944 (Box 6)
  - Hills, Consuela B. (3), Jan. 15, 1945, May 3, 1945, Nov. 6, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Hinstead, Ralph E. (2), Jan. 8, 1952, Aug. 10, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Hinds, Hayden and Eldredge, Inc. (1), May 2, 1917 (Box 6)
  - Hinrichs, Gerard (1), Mar. 17, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Hinson, Jack (1), Dec. 15, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Hinton, Dlmer (1), Jan. 5, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Hirsch, Sidney and Goldie (1), July 20, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Hirschman, Edw. F. (11), Nov. 1, 1949, Nov. 26, 1949, Oct. 3, 1950, Nov. 7, 1950, Feb. 5, 1951, Mar. 18, 1951, Apr. 5, 1951, July 27, 1951, July 2, 1952, Mar. 16, 1953, Aug. 20, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Hirschman, Ed and Grace (2), Dec. 19, 1949, Feb. 16, 1961 (Box 6)
  - Hoefle, Charles (1), Oct. 17, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Hoegger, J.A.Jr. (1), July 5, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Hoffman, Mrs. T.C. (1), Mar. 3, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Hoffmuster, Oscar (1), Jan. 7, 1 6 (Box 6)
  - Hofmann, W.F. (1), Oct. 8, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Holcomb, Sam Jr. (1), Feb. 10, 1946 (post card) (Box 6)
  - Holden, Chas. E. (16), Jan. 28, 1943, Feb. 7, 1943, Mar. 1, 1944, Mar. 17, 1944, Apr. 10, 1944, June 12, 1944, July 6, 1944, July 25, 1944, Aug. 5, 1944, Aug. 15, 1944, Sept. 27, 1944, Feb. 27, 1945, May 21, 1945, May 26, 1945, June 25, 1945, Sept. 5, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Holland, I.D. (1), Sept. 16, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Holman, Frank E. (1), Aug. 31, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Holmes, Roger W. (1), (n.d.) (Box 6)
  - Holt, C.S. (2), June 21, 1944 (post card), July 13, 1944 (post card) (Box 6)
  - Holt, Mrs. C.S. (1), Jan. 18, 1945 (post card) (Box 6)
  - Holt, Hamilton (1), Apr. 11, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Holt, Mrs.W.H. (2), Sept. 21, 1944, Oct. l, 1944 (Box 6)
  - Holzapfel, Ida D. (1), Nov. 28, 1949 (Box 6)
  - Holzapfel, J.N. (45), Dec. 13, 1943, Dec. 29, 1943, Feb. 9, 1944, Apr. 3, 1944, Apr. 15, 1944, May 22, 1944, July 22, 1944, Sept. 21, 1944, Sept. 22, 1944, Sept. 26, 1944, Oct. 15, 1944, Nov. 19, 1944, Uec. 4, 1944, Dec. 17, 1944, May 3, 1945, May 10, 1945; June 31 1945, July 11, 1945, Aug. 17, 1945, Aug. 23, 1945, Aug. 24, 1945Sept. 24, 1945, ec. 18, 1945, Dec. 27, 1945, Apr. 16, 1946, May 9, 1946, June 10, 1946, June 25, 1946, July 7, 1946, July 16, 1946, July 25, 1946, Aug. 1, 1946; Aug. 17, 1946, Sept. 2, 1946, Oct. 6, 1946, Oct. 20, 1946, Oct. 26, 1946, Nov. 3, 1946, Nov. 10, 1946, Nov. 13, 1946, Nov. 24, 1946, Feb. 28, 1947, Apr. 6, 1947, Dec. 7, 1947, Jan. 19, 1948 (Box 6)
  - Hooker, West (1), June 21, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Hope, E.R. (4), July 21, 1952, 1'eb. 9, 1953 (to Directors, Foreign Language Conference), Feb. 9, 1953, Feb. 26, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Hope, Earl and Mrs. (1), Dec. 5, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Hopkins, Sylvia D. (1), May 7, 1933 (Box 6)
  - Hopkins, Walter M. (2), May 28, 1945, Aug. 25, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Hopper, New Jersey Dog Owners Assn. (1), Nov. 12, 1952 (telegram) (Box 6)
  - Hopper, H.L. (1), Nov. 21, 1952 (Box 6)
  - Horswell, Laurence Alden (16), June 27, 1934 (to Mr.Foley), Feb. 14, 1935, Apr. 13, 1935, Apr. 20, 1935, June 11, 1935, July 14, 1935, July 17, 1935; Jan. 16, 1944, Aug. 24, 1944, Feb. 1, 1945 (post card), Nov. 15, 1945, Jan. 15, 1946, Aug. 12, 1946, Oct. 31, 1946, (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 6)
  - Horvay, William (1), Aug. 27, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Hosman, H.o. (1), Oct. 16, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Hostettler, John E. (1), Apr. 6, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Houchin, Mildred P. (4), Apr. 24, 1944 (post card), Nov. 14, 1944, Sept. 7, 1945 (post card), Jan. 3, 1946 (poet card) (Box 6)
  - Houghland, J.M. (1), Mar. 16, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Howard, Austin F. (2), Sept. 27, 1955; (n.d.) (Box 6)
  - Howard, Laurence B. (1), Jan. 28, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Howard, William F. (1), Aug. 18, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Howden, Charles Jr. (12), July 22, 1953, Sept. 3, 1954, Oct. 27, 1954, Feb. 2, 1955, Feb. 18, 1955, July 17, 1955, Aug. 4, 1955, Nov. 2, 1957, Jan. 3, 1958, Jan. 8, 1959, Nov. 11, 1959, Feb. 28, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Howden, Stell and Gharlie (1), June 7, 1954 (Box 6)
  - Howell, E.s. (1), Apr. 2, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Hoyt, Hayes Blake (1), Feb. 26, 1953 (to Mrs. Eugene D. Sullivan) (Box 6)
  - Huben, Alexander (1), Dec. 1, 1943 (Box 6)
  - Huck, Mildred A. (1), Oct. 31, 1957 (Box 6)
  - Huebener, Verna Riemann (28), Aug. 19, 1943 Jan. 3, 1944, Mar. 16, 1944, July 14, 1944, Sept. 1, 1944, Sept. 25, 1944, Nov. 14, 1944, Nov. 17, 1944, Vee. 13, 1944, (telegram), Dec. 11, 1944, Dec. 16, 1944 (telegram), Dec. 16, 1944 (telegram); Feb. 12, 1945, Feb. 20, 1945, Mar. 8, 1945, Mar.12, 1945, (telegram), Apr. 10, 1945, Apr. 28, 1945, May 16, 1945, May 29, 1945, July 30, 1945, Aug. 24, 1945, Nov. 12, 1945, Mar. 17, 1947, Dec. 7, 1951; Dec. 9, 1952, May 18, 1954, Aug. 28, 1957 (Box 6)
  - Hulin, Marion (2), Jan. 8, 1934, Aug. 21, 1934 (Box 6)
  - Hulsen, Bob (1), July 23, 1957 (to rtoland Lehr) (Box 6)
  - Hume, Mrs. Edgar (1), Oct. 27, 1943 (Box 6)
  - Humphrey, J.E. (1), Sept. 20, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Hunt, M.F. (1), Feb.ll, 1946 (post card) (Box 6)
  - Hunter, Paul (1), Jan. 13, 1922 (Box 6)
  - Huntington, W.E. (2), June 12, 1926, Oct. 24, 1927 (Box 6)
  - Hutchings, C.M. (3), Jan. 28, 1935, Feb. 26, 1935, Apr. 19, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Hyle, Gordon (1), Jan. 25, 1950 (Box 6)
  - Ilgner, Emil (1), June 25, 1937 (Box 7)
  - Iliff, James J. (1), Sept. 13, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Imes, Bernie (1), June 10, 1954 (Box 7)
  - Innes, aroline A. (1), May 16, 1948 (Box 7)
  - Irons, Elsie (5), Dec. 27, 1943, Dec. 29, 1943, Jan. 14, 1944, Jan. 31, 1944, Feb. 17, 1944 (Box 7)
  - Irtz, Frederick G. (7), Feb. 6, 1950, Feb. 6, 1950 (telegram), Jan. 8, 1952, Feb. 18, 1952, Mar. 7, 1952, June 3, 1952, (n.d.) (Box 7)
  - Irtz, Mrs.Frederick G. (2), Dec. 3, 1949, Jan. 2, 1950 (Box 7)
  - Ivins, Margot M. (1), June 25, 1944 (Box 7)
  - Ivy, Paul A.Jr. (1), Nov. 10, 1944 (Box 7)
  - Jackson, Chas. W. (1), Jan. 10, 1949 (Box 7)
  - Jackson, George Pullen (1), Oct. 25, 1944 (Box 7)
  - Jackson, George Pullen (the Family of) (1), Feb. 11, 1953 (Box 7)
  - Jacobe, A.M. (1), Feb. 11, 1946 (Box 7)
  - Jacobson, A.M. (1), May 9, 1949 (Box 7)
  - Jaeckel, Tracy (1), May 29, 1953 (Box 7)
  - Jaeger, William P.Jr. (1), Oct. 11, 1954 (Box 7)
  - von Jagemann, H.C.G. (2), Apr. 23, 1925, Sept. 18, 1925 (Box 7)
  - Jamal, Marie (1), Nov. 3, 1928 (Box 7)
  - James, T. White and o. (1) (Box 7)
  - Janssen, Jay (1), Jan. 11, 1945 (Box 7)
  - Jarvis, Arthur W. (1), Oct. 25, 1944 (Box 7)
  - Jasper, Elias (1), Nov. 19, 1955 (to J.Goodwin Knight) (Box 7)
  - Jefferson, Howard B. (1), Oct. 23, 1952 (Box 7)
  - Jeffery, H.E (1), Apr. 10, 1945 (to Mr. Martinoff) (Box 7)
  - Jeffrey, Henrys. (1), Aug. 29, 1913 (Box 7)
  - Jenkins, J.G. (1), Mar. 14, 1945 (Box 7)
  - Jenkins, O.D. (1), Apr. 8, 1944 (post card) (Box 7)
  - Jewe11s, W.B. (1), (n.d.) (Fragment (Box 7)
  - John, Mrs. C.R. (5), Oct. 4, 1946, Oct. 14, 1946, Oct. 21, 1946, Nov. 22, 1946, Dec. 14, 1946 (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Betty Haralson (2), Mar. 24, 1952, Aug. 5, 1952 (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Mr. and Mrs.Donald Verner (1) (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Edwin C. (1), Sept. 8, 1954 (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Everett W. (1), Feb. 14, 1945 (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Fred H. (1), Feb. 7, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Johnson, George B. (1), July 16, 1935 (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Harry M. (10), Apr. 9, 1928, June 30, 1928, Aug. 4, 1930, Oct. 25, 1935 (to Bruce H. Payne), Nov. 22, 1935, July 8; 1944, May 6, 1950, June 24, 1950, June 15, 1951, Oct. 30, 1952 (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Howard (1), May 15, 1961 (Box 7)
  - Johnson, James H. (1), Sept. 3, 1959 (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Mrs. Leon C. (4), Aug. 2, 1943, Mar. 1, 1944, Oct. 9, 1944, Oct. 14, 1948 (Box 7)
  - Johnson, T.C. (1), Nov. 2, 1937 (Box 7)
  - Johnston, Hulburd (3), Oct. 14, 1943, Mar.lO, 1947, Jan. 24, 1950 (Box 7)
  - Joint University Libraries (1), Sept. 28, 1955 (post card) (Box 7)
  - Joleling, Jas. W. (1), Oct. 10, 1950 (Box 7)
  - Jones, Arthur Frederick (2), Feb. 27, 1947, Vec. 3, 1948 (Box 7)
  - Jones, Bob Jr. (1), Oct. 15, 1943 (Box 7)
  - Jones, C. Hyland (1), June 20, 1942 (Box 7)
  - Jones, Cecil D. (2), Sept. 5, 1952, Sept. 10, 1952 (Box 7)
  - Jones, Charles A. (1), July 31, 1953 (Box 7)
  - Jones, J.M. (1), Feb. 10, 1946 (Box 7)
  - Joray, Juliette P. (1), June 11, 1957 (to C.A. Barden) (Box 7)
  - Jordan, George Racey (3), Sept. 23, 1958 (to Robert B. Anderson), Jan. 29, 1959 (to Frank C. Hannighen), Apr. 10, 1959 (Box 7)
  - Josephson, Emanuel M. (1), Apr. 26, 1955 (to Bluford H.J. Balter) (Box 7)
  - Judy, Will (3), Vee. 23, 1), Bept. 15, 1944, Nov. 2, 1950 (post card) (Box 7)
  - Kahn, Gwyneth (1), Feb. 6, 1950 (Box 7)
  - Kallen, H.M. (1), Oct. 31, 1934 (Box 7)
  - Kamphausen, Ernst (1), June 14, 1951 (Box 7)
  - Kandel, I.L. (2), Aug. 23, 1951 (post card), Aug. 30, 1951 (Box 7)
  - Kane, James (1), Oct. 15, 1952 (Box 7)
  - Kappa Delta (1), Dec. 1, 1950 (Box 7)
  - Karo, George (5), Apr. 22, 1944 (telegram), Apr. 24, 1944 (telegram), Apr. 24, 1944, Feb. 25, 1945, Feb. 25, 1945 (telegram) (Box 7)
  - Karten, David (1), Nov. 14, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Kasper, John (1), July 18, 1962 (Box 7)
  - Kattsoff, L.O. (4), Mar. 2, 1950, Oct. 24, 1952, May 24, 1955, Jan. 9, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Kaufman, Joseph S. (2), Sept. 13, 1943, Dec. 28, 1943 (Box 7)
  - Kaye, S.A. (2), Apr. 17, 1945, Jan. 21, 1952 (Box 7)
  - Keathley, J.H. (1), Oct. 14, 1959 (to E. Hodginson) (Box 7)
  - Keating, Micheline (1), Apr. 6, 1943 (Box 7)
  - Keifer, Fred B. (7), Sept. 8, 1943, Jan. 4, 1944, Jan. 21, 1944, Jan. 27, 1944, Feb. 10, 1944 (to Mrs. c. caswell), Apr. 25, 1944 (postcard), July 17, 1946 (Box 7)
  - Kelly, Alice s. (1), June 7, 1962 (Box 7)
  - Kelly, Nina (1), Feb. 1, 1945 (Box 7)
  - Kendrigan, James H. (2), Feb. 1, 1951, Mar. 2, 1951 (Box 7)
  - Kenimer, Jack (1), May 9, 1953 (Box 7)
  - Kenner, Lewis M. (3), Feb. 10, 1951, Mar. 10, 1951, Apr. 23, 1951 (Box 7)
  - Kenshalo, Dan R. (3), May 15, 1959, Jan. 4, 1960, Jan. 4, 1960 (Box 7)
  - Kerin, Austin H. (1), Sept. 2, 1955 (to Manuel and Lucille Miller) (Box 7)
  - * Kershaw, Jack (1), June 22, 1957 (Box 7)
  - Kershaw, Marian and Norman (24), Mar. 7, 1935, Aug. 19, 1935, Aug. 5, 1944, Oct. 19, 1944, Dec. 27, 1944, Feb. 17, 1945, Apr. 19, 1946, Oct. 23, 1946, May 14, 194 Aug. 16, 1949, Oct. 27, 1949, Dec. 12, 1949; Jan. 1950, Feb. 21, 1950, Mar. 28, 1950, Apr. 25, 1950, Jan. 12, 1952, Aug. 4, 1952, Aug. 15, 1955, Oct. 18, 1958, July 6, 1959, (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 7)
  - Kershaw, W.K. (1), Oct. 3, 1951 (Box 7)
  - Kettle, J. Harrison (1), Jan. 12, 1959 (Box 7)
  - Kiel, Buss W. (1), Nov. 7, 1919 (Box 7)
  - Kienast, Edith (1), Nov. 15, 1950 (Box 7)
  - Kiepe, Hans J. (2), July 8, 1945, Aug. 20, 1945 (Box 7)
  - Kimball, Edith H. (1), Oct. 15, 1952 (Box 7)
  - Kimball, Frank W. (6), Feb. 26, 1953, Aug. 29, 1954, Dec., 1957, Oct. 2, 1958, June 5, 1962 (post card), (n.d.) (Box 7)
  - King, Barrington J. (1), Feb. 25, 1944 (Box 7)
  - King, Dana M. (1), Nov. 26, 1934 (Box 7)
  - * Kershaw, Marian (8), Sept. 12, 1928, Dec. 18, 1944, Jan. 5, 1945, Feb. 1 1945, Jan. 27, 1947, Aug. 9, 1950, (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 7)
  - King, Dora A. (2), Mar. 4, 1935, June 2, 1935 (Box 7)
  - King, Earl Jr. (12), Feb. 16, 1950, Mar. 6, 1950, Aug. 6, 1950, Aug. 10, 1950, Mar. 21, 1951, Mar. 30, 1951, Dec. 31, 1951, May 6, 1952, Oct. 27, 1952, Mar. 26, 1959, Apr. 6, 1959, May 7, 1959 (Box 7)
  - King, W.A. (1), Mar. 28, 1935 (Box 7)
  - Kinsella, W.J.. Jr. (1), Oct. 1, 1945 (post card) (Box 7)
  - Kiplinger, W.W. (1), Feb. 17, 1945 (Box 7)
  - Kirk, John R. (1), Sept. 10, 1927 (Box 7)
  - Kirke, Mrs. William F. (1), Feb. 15, 1946 (Box 7)
  - Kirke, Mrs. (1), (n.d.) (Box 7)
  - Kirkland, J.H. (8), July 7, 1924, Feb. 2, 1925, June 4, 1925, June 16, 1925, Apr. 17, 1929, Apr. 19, 1929, Dec. 26, 1931, Dec. 14, 1934 (Box 7)
  - Kirkpatrick, W.H. (1), July 17, 1957 (Box 7)
  - Klages, K.H. (2), Mar. 9, 1950, May 18, 1950 (Box 7)
  - Klotz, Elsie (1), Nov. 9, 1951 (Box 7)
  - Knauss, Ernest (2), Apr. 10, 1935, July 8, 1935 (Box 7)
  - Knowland, William F. (1), June 10, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Knowles, James H. (1), Mar. 2, 1950 (Box 7)
  - Knox, Margaret Enid (1), Jan. 30, 1945 (Box 7)
  - Koenigsbauer, Joseph K. (1), Nov. 12, 1918 (Box 7)
  - Kohanski, Alexander (5), Aug. 14, 1934, May 14, 1935, July 5, 1935, Aug. 7, 1935, June 9, 1953 (Box 7)
  - Kohn, Mrs. Stephen (1), Feb. 5, 1935 (Box 7)
  - Kolb, s. Denmead (2), Apr. 1, 1953, May 1, 1953 (Box 7)
  - Kord, C.E. (6), May 24, 1945 (to Mrs. w.c. Huebener), Nov. 29, 1946 (to Frances Anthofer), May 12, 1950 (to Sidney J. Twining), May 2, 1951, (to Francis Dooley), Nov. 28, 1952, Mar. 24, 1953 (Box 7)
  - Kortmacher, W.C. (3), Sept. 25, 1952, Apr. 26, 1955, May 24, 1955 (to Joseph Hausladen) (Box 7)
  - Kotkov, Caroline and David (2), Feb. 18, 1946; Feb. 18 (n.d.) (Box 7)
  - Kotkov, David (3), Mar. 21, 1947, Oct. 31, 1950; (n.d.) (Box 7)
  - Krampf, Wilhelm (6), Oct. 26, 1951, Dec. 9, 1951, Aug. 1, 1954, Sept. 4 1954, Jan. 4, 1955 (post card), Oct. 30, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Kregel's Book Store (1), June 20, 1944 (Box 7)
  - Kroner, Richard (1), Oct. 8, 1953 (Box 7)
  - Kuhlman, A.F. (2), Oct. 4, 1955, Feb. 22, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Kuttner, Robert (1), Apr. 11, 1959 (Box 7)
  - Lacey, Oliver L. (5), Mar. 9, 1953, Mar. 10, 1953, Apr. 16, 1953, Mar. 10, 1954, May 4, 1954 (Box 8)
  - Ladd, TomE. (2), May 18, 1950; Jan. 16, 1953 (Box 8)
  - Lancaster, H.C. (1), Feb. 23, 1951 (Box 8)
  - Langan, Winifred E. (1), Jan. 22, 1953 (Box 8)
  - Langfeld, Herbert S. (2), May 13,1929, June 3, 1929 (Box 8)
  - Langford, Walter M. (1), Jan. 25, 1956 (Box 8)
  - Lang!Porne, Curtis (2), Apr. 5, 1954, Oct. 27, 1954 (to Joseph E. Moore) (Box 8)
  - Langrod, John (1), May 4, 1955 (Box 8)
  - Lanier, Lyle H. (9), Sept. 27, 1927, Sept. 14, 1944 (to C.P. Heinlein), Sept. 16, 1944, Oct. 11, 1944, Jan. 31, 1945 (to Dr. Meltzer), Dec. 19, 1945, Nov. 21, 1945, Jan. 5, 1947, Apr. 19, 1955 (Box 8)
  - Larkin, Thomas (2), Dec. 31, 1945, Apr. 18, 1951 (Box 8)
  - Lasch, Earl H. (1), Dec. 17, 1952 (Box 8)
  - Late, Mrs. Robt. W. (1), July 11, 1946 (Box 8)
  - Latourette, Evelyn (4), Aug. 22, 1944, Apr. 9, 1945, Apr. 24, 1945, May 12, 1945 (Box 8)
  - Laufle, Charlesw. (1), Oct. 22, 1943 (Box 8)
  - Law, O.H. (1), June 19, 1935 (Box 8)
  - Lawrence, David (3), Mar. 18, 1954, Aug. 27, 1954, Oct. 1, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Laws, P.G. (1), (n.d.) (Box 8)
  - LeBlond, R.E. (3), May 2, 1944, May 15, 1944, Aug. 2, 1944 (Box 8)
  - LeFevre, Robert (1), June 13, 1955 (Box 8)
  - LeSourd, Howard M. (1), Feb. 20, 1935 (Box 8)
  - Lea, R.M. (3), Aug. 10, 1944, Mar. 30, 1945 (post card), Dec. 1, 1949 (post card) (Box 8)
  - Leach, carl A. (4), July 23, 1943, Oct. 23, 1943, (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 8)
  - Leake, Chauncy D. (1), Oct. 2, 1945 (to Frank Pattie) (Box 8)
  - Leavitt, Sturgis E. (1), May 19, 1954 (Box 8)
  - Lee, Arthur N. (3), June 28, 1954, June 28, 1954, July 20, 1954 (Box 8)
  - Lee, FrankM. (1), Aug. 27, 1951 (Box 8)
  - Lee, Harold N. (2), Mar. 9, 1950, Apr. 14, 1950 (Box 8)
  - Lee, J. Bracken (1), Jan. 27, 1956 (Box 8)
  - Lee, Jack W. (1), (n.d.) (Box 8)
  - Lehmann, William C. (4), Apr. 2, 1944, Sept. 6, 1944, Sept. 17, 1944 (Oost card), Dec. 24, 1944 (Box 8)
  - Lehr, Linda (2), Dec. 30, 1949; (n.d.) (Box 8)
  - Lehr, Roland (113), May 26, 1943, Aug. 24, 1943, Oct. 15, 1943, Oct. 18, 1943, Oct. 25, 1943, Nov. 5, 1943, Mar. 16, 1944, Mar 16, 1944, Mar. 24, 1944, Mar. 29, 1944, Apr. 1, 1944, Apr. 1, 1944, Aprl. 1, 1944, Apr. 3, 1944, Apr. 8, 1944, Apr. 14, 1944; Apr. 17, 1944, May 2, 194 May 9, 1944, May 15, 1944 (telegram), May 29, 1944, June 3, 1944, June 12, 1944, June 19, 1944, June 19, 1944 (telegram), July 10, 1944, July 10, 1944, July 12, 1944, July 18, 1944, Aug. 1,1944, Aug. 26, 1944; Sept. 12, 1944, Sept. 12, 1944, Oct. 14, 1944, Oct. 21, 1944, Oct. 23, 1944, Dec. 5, 1944, Feb. 27, 1945, Mar. 19, 1945, Mar. 26, 1945, Mar. 27, 1945, Mar. 29, 1945, Mar. 29, 1945, Apr. 7, 1945, Apr. 14, 1945, June 15, 1945; July 3, 1945, July 24, 1945, July 30, 1945, Aug. 8,1945, Aug. 21, 1945, Sept. 19, 1945, Nov. 1, 1945, Nov. 12, 1945, Nov. 19, 1945, Nov. 19, 1945, Nov. 20, 1945; Dec. 3, 1945, Dec. 7, 1945, Dec. 7, 1945, Jan., 4, 1946, Feb. 4, 1946, Feb. 27, 1946; Mar. 6, 1946, Mar. 19, 1946, Mar. 21, 1946 (telegram), Mar. 21, 1946, Apr. 1, 1946, May 8, 1946, May 17, 1946, May 21, 1946, May 22, 1946; June 26, 1946, July 8, 1946, July 18, 1946, July 31, 1946, Sept. 4, Sept. 9, 1946, Oct. 21, 1946, Nov. 1, 1946; Jan. 3, 1947, Jan. 9, 1947, Jan. 18, 1947, Jan. 22, 1947, Feb. 27, 1947, Mar. 21, 1947, Mar. 24, 1947, May 8, 1947, Mar. 15, 1948 (post card), June 22, 1948; June 28, 1948, June 6, 1949, Oct. 3, 1949, Oct. 14, 1949 (telegram), Nov. 15, 1949, Dec. 28, 1949; Feb. 23, 1950, Mar. 8, 1950, Apr. 12, 1950, July 10, 1950,Aug. 21, 1950, Jan. 2, 1952, Aug. 21, 1952, Oct. 8, 1952, Oct. 10, 1952; Apr. 21, 1953 (post card), Mar. 26, 1954, Sept. 6, 1955, Aug. 2, 1956, July 26, 1957, Apr. 28, 1959, Sept. 9, 1959, Jan. 27, 1960 (Box 8)
  - Leidecker, Kurt F. (1), Jan. 1949 (Box 8)
  - Leighton, Joseph Alexander (2), Mar. 13, 1923, Mar. 8, 1928 (Box 8)
  - Leisher, Quentin (1), July 8, 1955 (Box 8)
  - Lemard, W.E. (1), Oct. 22, 1927 (Box 8)
  - Lenier, Mrs. H. (1), July 13, 1945 (Box 8)
  - Leniter, Leonard J. (1), JUly 31, 1946 (Box 8)
  - Leonard, Albert (1), Dec. 15, 1944 (Box 8)
  - Leonpacher, Fanny M. (1), Mar. 27, 1950 (Box 8)
  - Letson, stanley W.I. (1), Oct. 28, 1952 (Box 8)
  - Lewis, Fred J. (1), Dec. 2, 1949 (Box 8)
  - Lewis, Fulton Jr. (1), Apr. 5, 1951 (Box 8)
  - Liddell, Anna Forbes (5), Jan. 7, 1950, Mar. 22, 1950, Oct. 26, 1951, Oct. 12, 1954, July 18, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Lidstone, Maude (1), Feb. 28, 1932 (Box 8)
  - Lincoln, Frederick C. (2), Jan. 9, 1951, Nov. 19, 1951 (Box 8)
  - Linfitt, Chas. A. (1), Oct. 24, 1935 (Box 8)
  - Link, Grover c. (1), May 1, 1953 (Box 8)
  - Lippincott, Tom (1), May 2, 1940 (Box 8)
  - Lipscomb, Maggie and Herbert (1), Oct. 20, 1936 (Box 8)
  - Little, C.C. (9), May 7, 1924, Nov. 27, 1935, Apr. 4, 1945, May 19, 1945 June 13, 1945, Sept. 6, 1945, Sept. 17, 1945 (tele gram), Jan. 22, 1946, June 28, 1946 (Box 8)
  - Little, Charles E. (1), Apr. 7, 1936 (Box 8)
  - Little, L.H. (1), June 20, 1955 (Box 8)
  - Littlejohn, Doctor and Mrs. Wilmot Shipp (1), Sept. 9, 1954 (Box 8)
  - Locke, W.D. (1), Dec. 4, 1945 (Box 8)
  - Locke, Leon (1), Jan. 9, 1935 (Box 8)
  - Loeb, William (1), Feb. 10, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Loemker, Roy (2), June 6, 1958, Jan. 16, 1963 (Box 9)
  - Loessel, Lenard (1), Oct. 9, 1935 (Box 9)
  - Long, L.J. (1), Nov. 26, 1951 (to Bennet H. Branscomb) (Box 9)
  - Longshore, Helen M. (2), Dec. 20, 1955, June 5, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Longshore, Jack M. (2), Dec. 15, 1953, Aug. 1, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Loomis, Margaret (1), Dec. 27, 1943 (Box 9)
  - Losch, William F. Jr. (1), May 16,1952 (Box 9)
  - Lou, Ida M. (1), Dec. 23, 1944 (outgoing letter from Sanborn included on this incoming letter) (Box 9)
  - Louisville Courier-Journal (1), (n.d.) (Box 9)
  - Louisville Dachshund Club (1), July 19, 1957 (Box 9)
  - Love, Earnest C. (1), Feb. 26, 1951 (Box 9)
  - Lovejoy, Arthur O. (1), Feb. 7, 1928 (Box 9)
  - Loves, Joe Brown (1), Sept. 30, 1954 (Box 9)
  - Lowe, Herbert (1), Aug. 19, 1946 (to Alexander Martinoff) (Box 9)
  - Lowenhein, Mary Jane (1), Dec. 25, 1929 (post card) (Box 9)
  - Lukens, Florence (1), Apr. 1, 1947 (Box 9)
  - Lutz, Ann (1), Dec. 18, 1945 (Box 9)
  - Lutz, Edith A. (1), Nov. 5, 1939 (Box 9)
  - Lutz, Louis (2), Jan. 30, 1954, Mar. 10, 1954 (Box 9)
  - Lutz, M.S. (1), July 17, 1945 (Box 9)
  - Lutz, William S. (1), Dec. 28, 1935 (Box 9)
  - Lyle, Ernestine R. (1), July 22, 1954 (Box 9)
  - Lyle, Richard H. (1), Apr. 27, 1959 (Box 9)
  - Lyman, J.C. (1), Jan. 22, 1943 (Box 9)
  - Lynch, William F. (1), June 3, 1954 (Box 9)
  - Lyons, Janes A., Jr. (2), July 17, 1957, Apr. 7, 1958 (Box 9)
  - Lyons, Mrs. J.A. Jr. (2), Sept. 12, 1957, Oct. 2, 1957 (Box 9)
  - Lytle, Andrew (3), Jan. 4, 1949; Sept. 17, 1955, Feb. 11, 1958 (Box 9)
  - MacClintock, Stuart (2), Nov. 22, 1957, Jan. 1, 1958 (Box 9)
  - MacDonald, Edna Gray B. (1), Jan. 31, 1955 (Box 9)
  - MacFarland, W. Henry Jr. (2), Dec. 3, 1955, Dec. 1955 (Box 9)
  - McAllister, Andrew B. (1), Apr. 1, 1955 (Box 9)
  - McCall, Gertrude Lewis (1), Oct. 30, 1954 (Box 9)
  - McCarthy, Joe (1), Nov. 20, 1952 (Box 9)
  - McClure, M.T. (1), Apr. 3, 1951 (Box 9)
  - McCOmas, H.C. (1), July 16, 1946 (Box 9)
  - McCo d, Virginia N. (1), Dec. 14, 1945 (Box 9)
  - McCornick, L.S. (1), May 13, 1929 (Box 9)
  - McCormick, Robert R. (3), Dec. 21, 1943, Sept. 5, 1952, Sept. 17, 1952 (Box 9)
  - McCoy, Frank T. (1), Feb. 10, 1945 (Box 9)
  - McCoy, Louise Hardison (1), July 21, 1951 (Box 9)
  - McDermott, John Francis (1), June 10, 1931 (Box 9)
  - McDevitt, John J. (1), Apr. 1, 1932 (Box 9)
  - McDonnell, June (6), May 10, 1946 (post card), May 12, 1946, June 17, 1946, (post card), July 5, 1946, Jan. 17, 1950, Apr. 27, 1953 (Box 9)
  - McDougall, Wylie (1), Mar. 29, 1955 (Box 9)
  - McGee, A.J. (1), May 19, 1953 (Box 9)
  - McGee, Paul (1), Feb. 24, 1959 (Box 9)
  - McGehee, Edward (1), Oct. 5, 1943 (Box 9)
  - McGinley, Conde (5), Sept. 15, 1954, Nov. 26, 1954, Jan. 13, 1956, (nd.), (n.d.) (Box 9)
  - McGregor, J.H. (1), Apr. 22, 1929 (Box 9)
  - McGurk, F.C.J. (1), Nov. 26, 1956 (Box 9)
  - McHarg, Ormsby (2), Feb. 28, 1945, Feb. 5, 1946 (Box 9)
  - McHugh, Mrs. Philip (1), Aug. 3, 1951 (Box 9)